Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Anthony J. Viola Papers, 1968-2009 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2009 and undated, (17 boxes) (Box 20)
  - Originals, 1970-2008 and undated (Box 20)
    - Umatic and VHS (Box 20)
      - 72. Sample Reel. 1989 Jan. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for Sunkist; Acutrim; Merita; and Hendries]
      - 73. Sample Reel. 1989. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 29)
        [Includes spots for Merita; Acutrim; Hendries; and Sunkist]
      - 74. Sample Reel. 1989. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
      - 75. Sample Reel. 1990 Feb. 8. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Merita; Dole; Sunkist; Hendries; and Kodak]
      - 76. Sample Reel. 1990 Feb. 8. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
      - 77. Sample Reel. 1990 Feb. 8. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Dole; Merita; Sunkist; Hendries; and Kodak]
      - 78. Sample Reel. 1990 Feb. 26. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Nestea; Dole; Acutrim; Merita; Sunkist; Hendries; and Kodak]
      - 79. Sample Reel. 1990 Feb. 28. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Sunkist; Acutrim; Hendries; and Merita]
      - 80. Sample Reel--International. 1993 Oct. 15. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Merita; Hendries; Nestea; Kelloggs; Sunkist; and Kodak]
      - 81. Sample Reel--International. 1993 Oct. 15. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 30)
        [Includes spots for Mimosa and Sumol]
      - 82. Sample Reel. 1993. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
      - 83. Sample Reel. 2004 Aug. 10. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
        [Includes spots for Cottonelle; Trident; Halls Fruit Breezers; Listerine; Lubriderm; and Lipton Iced Tea]
      - 84. Sample Reel--Domestic. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
      - 85. Sample Reel--International. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
      - 86. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00. (Box 31)
        [Includes spots for Kodak and Burger King]
      - 87. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
        [Includes spots for Merita and Hendries]
      - 88. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 31)
      - 89. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 31)
      - 90. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
        [Includes spots for Schlitz; Oscar Mayer; Kodak; Jovan; and Kraft]
      - 91. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
        [Includes spots for City of Boston and Sears Jeans]
      - 92. Sample Reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
        [Includes spots for Schlitz; Kodak; and Kraft]
      - 93. Television-Print-Sketches. 1988. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
        [Includes spots for Kelloggs; Nestea; Dole; Merita; Hendries; and Kodak]
      - 94. Television-Print-Sketches. 1989 Jan. 30. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
      - 95. Television-Print-Sketches. 1989 Jan. 30. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
      - 96. Television-Print-Sketches. 1989 Feb. 03. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
      - 97. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 32)
      - 98. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 99. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 100. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 101. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 102. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 103. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 104. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 105. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 33)
      - 106. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown. (Box 34)
      - 107. Television-Print-Sketches. Undated. VHS. TRT: unknown. (Box 34)
        [Includes spots for Kellogs; Nestea; Dole; Merita; and Kodak]
      - 108. Tony Viola Title Only. Undated. Umatic. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 109. No title. Undated. VHS. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 110. Australia--Getting Down to Buisness 1998 Aug. VHS. TRT: 11:30 (Box 34)
    - DVD (Box 34)
      - 111. Band-aid. 2008 Jan 17. DVD. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 112. Band-aid--Sales Film. 2008 Jan 28. DVD. TRT: 1:31 (Box 34)
      - 113. Glass Plus. 2006 Nov. 14. DVD. TRT: :45 (Box 34)
      - 114. Glass Plus. 2006 Nov. 22. DVD. TRT: :45 (Box 34)
      - 115. Health Club Animatic. 2005 Nov. 2. DVD. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 116. Listerine. 2008 Oct. 10. DVD. TRT: :30 (Box 34)
      - 117. Listerine Whitening. 2007 Oct. 15. DVD. TRT: 2:14 (Box 34)
      - 118. Lysol Disenfectant. 2005 May 24. DVD. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 119. Neutra Air. 2007 Jan. 05. DVD. TRT: :60 (Box 34)
      - 120. Pristiq. 2008 Apr. 07. DVD. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 121. Reach. 2007 Oct. 16. DVD. TRT: unknown (Box 34)
      - 122. Visine. 2009 Mar. 18. DVD. TRT: :30 (Box 34)
      - 124. Presentation Reel--Syracuse University. 2005 Jul. 11. DVD. TRT: unknown. (Box 34)
        [Includes spots for Cottonelle; Halls Fruit Breezers; Listerine; Lubriderm; Lipton Iced Tea; Neosporin; and Kodak]
    - 16mm Film and Video Reels (Box 34)
      - 125. Acutrim. 1989 Dec. 14. 1 inch video. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 126. Acutrim. 1990 Jan. 18. 1 inch video. TRT: :15 (Box 35)
      - 127. Acutrim. 1990 Feb. 15. 1 inch video. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 128. Acutrim. 1990 Apr. 11. 1 inch video. TRT: :90 (Box 35)
      - 129. Anco. 1979 Nov. 08. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 130. Boston. 1970-1975. 16mm film. TRT: unknown. (Box 35)
        [Includes spots for City of Boston; Better Home Heat; New England Merchants; Underwood; B&M Beans; United Way; Canal Bank; Polaroid; Boston Bicentennial; Boston Red Sox and Sears Jeans]
      - 131. Canal Bank. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: unknown (Box 35)
      - 132. Get A Way Banana. Undated. 1 inch video. TRT: unknown (Box 35)
      - 133. Godspell. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 134. Hendries. 1990 Jan. 19. 1 inch video. TRT: :60 (Box 35)
      - 135. Kraft Mayonnaise. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 136. Merita Lite Bread. 1990 Jan. 03. 1 inch video. TRT: :80 (Box 35)
      - 137. Mirro. 1978 Oct. 10. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 138. Nestea. 1983 May 19. 1 inch video. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 139. Oil Heat Association. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 140. Oscar Mayer Cold Cuts Construction Worker. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 141. Oscar Mayer Cold Cuts Librarian. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 142. Oscar Mayer Cold Cuts Mr. Efficiency. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 143. Pepsi. 1986 Feb. 13. 1 inch video. TRT: 3:30 (Box 35)
      - 144. Perx. 1986 Oct. 06. 1 inch video. TRT: :60 (Box 35)
      - 145. Schlitz Give it the Look. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 146. Schlitz Great 8. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :10 (Box 35)
      - 147. Schlitz Great Tasting Beer. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :10 (Box 35)
      - 148. Schlitz Millions/Go for it. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 149. Schlitz There is a Beer. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 150. Sears Denim Jeans. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 151. Sears Men's Store. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: :30 (Box 35)
      - 152. Sunkist Vitamins. 1990 Jan. 18. 1 inch video. TRT: :15 (Box 35)
      - 153. Water Pitcher. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: unknown (Box 35)
      - 154. Sample Reel. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: unknown. (Box 35)
        [Includes spots for SMS Jeans and Underwood]
      - 155. Sample Reel. Undated. 16mm film. TRT: unknown. (Box 35)
        [Includes spots for SMS Jeans; New England Merchant; and Pewter Pot]
      - 156. Sample Reel. 1978-1980. 16mm film. TRT: unknown (Box 35)
    - Betacam (Box 35)
      - 157. Listerine Mouthwash. 2003 Apr. 22. Betacam. TRT: :30 (Box 36)
      - 158. Lubriderm. 2001 Apr. 26. Betacam. TRT: :30 (Box 36)
      - 159. Neosporin. 2005 Mar. 17. Betacam. TRT: :75 (Box 36)
      - 160. Scott Tissues. 2000 Apr. 21. Betacam. TRT: :45 (Box 36)
      - 161. Scott Towels. 2002 Mar. 07. Betacam. TRT: :45 (Box 36)
      - 162. Sumol. 1993 Jul. 28. Betacam. TRT: unknown (Box 36)
      - 163. Presentation Reel. Syracuse University. 2000 Sept. 15. Betacam. TRT: unknown (Box 36)
  - Preservation Masters (Box 36)
    - Anthony Viola Television 1970s-2000s, 2009. Betacam. TRT: unknown (Box 37)
  - Use copies of audiovisual materials, 2009 (Box 37)
    - Tony Viola Scans, Storyboards, Advertisements/Art, TV Boards, 2009 May 7, DVD (Box 1)
    - Anthony Viola Television 1970s-2000s, 2009 May 14, DVD (Box 1)
      [Contents include: 1970s: Underwood canned meats; B&M Baked Beans; Canal Bank; WSBK TV-38/Boston Red Sox; Mass Bay United Fund/United Way; Polaroid SX-70 camera; Better Home Heat Council; New England Merchants National Bank; Mayor's Older Bostonians; Jovan; Boston Bicentennial; Sears Thumb's Up Jeans; Schlitz]
      [1980s: Oscar Mayer lunch meats; Kraft Mayonnaise; Nestea tea bags; Kodak (commercials in Portuguese, English and Spanish); Jake's Diet Cola; Pepsi (in Spanish)]
      [1990s: Kellogg's Bran Flakes; Merita Lite Bread; Sunkist Children's Multivitamins; You yogurt drink (in Portuguese); Mimosa yogurt (in Portuguese); Sumol drink (in Portuguese); Listerine; Lubriderm]
      [2000s: Lubriderm; Bufferin; Kellogg's Breakfast Mates; Scott tissue and towels; Cottonelle Rollwipes; Neosporin; Lipton Iced Tea; Lysol for Kitchen; Hall's Fruit Breezers; Listerine; Reach toothbrushes; Animatics (Neutra-Air; Glass Plus; Purell; Lysol Wipes; Listerine; Visine)]